What do you mean Freya's the reason why Ci-N is in Section E?
프레야의 이유가 뭔데? 왜 Ci-N이 섹션 E에 있나요?
Ci-N kissed me.
Ci-N이 나에게 키스했다.
And Freya got mad because…
그리고 프레야는 화를 냈는데...
apparently, she likes Ci-N too.
아무래도 그녀도 Ci-N을 좋아하는 모양이다.
So, we got into a fight and she made stories about Ci-N.
그래서 우리는 싸움을 벌였고, 그녀는 Ci-N에 대한 이야기를 만들었습니다.
After that, everyone accused Ci-N of being a thief.
그 후 모두가 고소당했습니다. 도둑의 Ci-N.
Ci-N, a thief? He's too childish for that.
씨엔, 도둑? 그러기엔 그 사람이 너무 유치해요.
Hey, he's not childish.
이봐, 그 사람은 유치하지 않아.
You want pancakes?
팬케이크 먹을래?
You offered, but it's not cooked. You're really something else, kid.
제안했지만 요리되지 않았습니다. 넌 정말 뭔가 달라졌어, 꼬마야.
Then just cook it.
그럼 그냥 요리하세요.
Is that him?
그 사람인가요?
He stole it!
그가 훔쳤어요!
Are you sure? You have proof?
확실합니까? 증거가 있나요?
Don't butt in!
끼어들지 마세요!
What if I punch you in the mouth?!
내가 네 입에 주먹을 날리면 어쩌지?!
- I will really do it! - Jay-jay, just let them be!
- 정말 할게요! - 제이제이, 그냥 놔둬요!
Oh my…
이런...
Ci-N. You did it again?
Ci-N. 또 그랬어?
Why didn't you tell me?!
왜 나한테 말하지 않았어?!
I'm scared you'll look at me differently.
당신이 나를 다르게 볼까봐 두렵습니다.
It's as if you're proving that what they're saying is true!
증명하고 있는 것 같군요 그 사람들 말이 사실이라니!
Jay-jay!
제이제이!
Why did you do that?
왜 그랬어요?
I miss my friends from Section E.
섹션 E의 친구들이 그리워요.
And Ci-N is one of them.
Ci-N도 그중 하나입니다.
That's the money you paid that bitch!
그게 네가 그년한테 낸 돈이잖아!
Ci-N didn't steal that!
Ci-N은 그것을 훔치지 않았습니다!
I did!
내가 그랬어!
I'll pay for the cafe's entire earnings for the day.
카페 비용은 내가 다 지불할게 오늘의 수입.
Just get rid of all the customers here.
여기 있는 고객을 모두 제거하세요.
Most especially the judgmental ones.
특히 판단하는 것들이요.
Here it comes.
여기 온다.
Excuse me, Ma'am, Sir.
죄송합니다, 부인, 선생님.
Here's your order.
주문 내용은 다음과 같습니다.
Coffee.
커피.
Iced tea.
아이스 티.
Enjoy your meal.
식사를 즐기십시오.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Here. Eat up.
여기. 먹어라.
About time. I'm so famished.
시간쯤. 너무 배가 고파요.
I've been biking a long way.
나는 오랫동안 자전거를 타고 왔습니다.
I'm drenched in sweat. I'm so hungry.
땀에 흠뻑 젖었어요. 너무 배가 고파요.
Mmmm.
음.
It's so tasty!
너무 맛있어요!
Why?
왜?
Hmm?
흠?
Why did you do that for Ci-N?
Ci-N을 위해 왜 그랬나요?
Ci-N is like a brother to me.
Ci-N은 나에게 형제와도 같다.
You know that feeling when...
그 기분 아시죠...
an older sister can't bear to see her brother get hurt?
언니는 참을 수 없다 오빠가 다치는 걸 보려고?
That's how it felt.
그 느낌이 그랬습니다.
Don't you have any siblings?
형제자매가 없나요?
Why do you care so much for Ci-N?
왜 Ci-N에 그렇게 관심을 두나요?
I wasn't informed this is gonna be an interview.
난 이런 소식을 몰랐어 인터뷰가 될 거예요.
I'm just curious.
그냥 궁금해서요.
My Auntie told me I had an older brother.
이모가 나한테 말했어 나에게는 형이 있었다.
But my mom put him up for adoption.
그런데 엄마가 그 아이를 입양 보내셨어요.
I never met him.
나는 그를 만난 적이 없습니다.
What's up? Have you told Jay yet?
무슨 일이야? Jay에게 아직 말하지 않았나요?
How about you? Don't you have any siblings?
당신은 어떤가요? 형제자매가 없나요?
I do. She's in Japan. With my parents.
그래요. 그녀는 일본에 있어요. 부모님과 함께.
She's eight years younger than me.
그녀는 나보다 8살 어리다.
Edrix, where are you?
에드릭스, 어디야?
We just finished playing basketball. We're starving. Let's go eat!
우리는 방금 농구를 마쳤어요. 우리는 배고프다. 먹으러 가자!
I'll be there.
나는 거기 있을 것이다.
[Yuri laughs]
[유리 웃는다]
It's delicious.
맛있어요.
This is so good!
정말 좋아요!
I shouldn't be feeling this way. I'm confused...
이렇게 느껴서는 안 됩니다. 혼란스러워요...
All this time, I thought I loved Ella.
이번에는 내가 Ella를 사랑한다고 생각했어요.
But fuck. I will no longer deny it.
하지만 젠장. 나는 더 이상 그것을 부정하지 않을 것이다.
I'm starting to feel something for Jay-jay.
제이제이에게 뭔가 감정이 들기 시작했어요.
Delicious!
맛있는!
I've finished it.
나는 그것을 마쳤다.
But why her of all people?
그런데 왜 그녀는 누구일까요?
Why did I fall for the person Keifer hates?
나는 왜 Keifer가 싫어하는 사람에게 반했나요?
I'm the only one eating. You might say I'm a glutton.
나만 먹고 있어요. 당신은 내가 대식가라고 말할 수도 있습니다.
Here's some more.
여기에 몇 가지가 더 있습니다.
Don't you want some?
좀 원하지 않나요?
Keifer's just gonna use her.
Keifer가 그녀를 이용하려고 합니다.
I don't know how, but I don't want to see it nor imagine it.
방법은 모르겠지만 원하지 않습니다. 그것을 보거나 상상할 수 없습니다.
I don't think I can bear seeing Jay-jay in tears.
나는 견딜 수 없을 것 같아요 제이제이가 눈물을 흘리는 모습을 보고 있습니다.
This tastes similar to the muffins Auntie Gemma makes.
머핀이랑 맛이 비슷해요 젬마 아줌마가 만듭니다.
Have you ever had a boyfriend?
남자친구가 있었던 적 있나요?
Huh?!
뭐?!
Why the sudden question?
갑자기 질문은 왜?
I'm just asking.
그냥 물어보는 거야
I have.
나는 가지고있다.
Really?
정말?
Why do you sound so surprised?
왜 그렇게 놀란 것 같나요?
As if I'm too ugly to have a relationship.
내가 너무 못생긴 것처럼 관계를 갖기 위해.
It's not that. What I mean is...
그게 아닙니다. 내 말은...
But it's true. I had two.
하지만 사실이에요. 나는 두 개를 가지고 있었다.
What happened? Why did you break up?
무슨 일이에요? 왜 헤어졌나요?
The first one...
첫 번째는...
he came out. Apparently, he's actually gay.
그는 나왔다. 분명히, 그 사람 사실은 게이예요.
The second one...
두 번째는...
he's in the hospital.
그는 병원에 있어요.
Comatose.
기운 없이 졸리는.
Why? What happened?
왜? 무슨 일이에요?
I don't remember anymore.
더 이상 기억이 나지 않습니다.
Anyway. Let's not talk about it.
그래도. 그것에 대해 이야기하지 말자.
How about you? Share something about your love life.
당신은 어떤가요? 당신의 연애 생활에 대해 이야기해 보세요.
Oh, me?
아, 나?
Nothing serious.
심각한 것은 아닙니다.
But I fell in love once.
하지만 나는 한 번 사랑에 빠졌습니다.
And she didn't love me back.
그리고 그녀는 나를 다시 사랑하지 않았습니다.
Was it Ella?
엘라였나요?
Oh...
아...
sorry.
죄송합니다.
That's okay. It's all in the past.
괜찮습니다. 그것은 모두 과거의 일입니다.
Really? Is that so?
정말? 그렇습니까?
You're annoying.
당신은 짜증나.
There's Ella!
저기 엘라가 있어요!
[Jay-jay chuckles]
[제이제이가 웃는다]
You're so annoying, Jay.
너 정말 짜증나, 제이.
Eat something too.
너도 뭔가 먹어라.
Go on. I don't really eat those.
계속하세요. 저는 그런 것들은 잘 안 먹어요.
Then why did you order them?
그럼 왜 주문하셨나요?
No idea.
모르겠어요.
You're really out of it!
정말 정신이 없군요!
How will you go home later?
나중에 집에 어떻게 갈 거예요?
I'll ride my bike. It's too tiring, honestly.
나는 자전거를 탈 것이다. 솔직히 너무 피곤해요.
It's too far away. I got drenched in sweat.
너무 멀다. 땀에 흠뻑 젖었어요.
Shall I take you home?
집에 데려다 드릴까요?
Mmm?
음?
Keif.
케이프.
Hey.
여기요.
Damn.
젠장.
What's his problem?
그 사람의 문제는 무엇입니까?
You're in a bad mood, Keif?
기분이 안 좋나요, 케이프?
That's why I followed.
그래서 나는 따라갔다.
It's the Jay-jay situation.
제이제이 상황입니다.
It's a mess.
엉망이에요.
So...
그럼...
what's the plan?
계획은 뭐야?
Hopefully, Edrix can hack the CCTV records.
Edrix가 CCTV 기록을 해킹할 수 있기를 바랍니다.
Find proof that Ci-N didn't steal anything.
Ci-N이 아무것도 훔치지 않았다는 증거를 찾아보세요.
Almost done bypassing the firewall.
방화벽 우회가 거의 완료되었습니다.
And then, I just need to decrypt the storage files.
그럼 난 그냥 해야겠어 저장 파일의 암호를 해독합니다.
Wait...
잠깐...
Someone blocked my access!
누군가 내 접근을 차단했어요!
Huh?
뭐?
I can't get in! What the hell!
들어갈 수 없어요! 도대체 무슨 일이야!
- I need to re-route. - I'm too dumb for this stuff.
- 경로를 다시 바꿔야 해요. - 난 이런 일을 하기에는 너무 멍청해요.
Hold on, hold on.
잠깐만요, 잠깐만요.
Damn!
젠장!
What?!
무엇?!
The system locked me out!
시스템이 나를 차단했습니다!
Sorry, Keif.
미안해요, 케이프.
Can't get it this time around.
이번에는 구할 수 없습니다.
I still can't get inside the CCTV record archives.
아직은 들어갈 수 없어 CCTV 기록 보관소.
You did your best.
당신은 최선을 다했습니다.
Why don't we just get a copy from the admin?
그냥 가져가는 게 어때? 관리자의 사본?
That's right.
좋아요.
Are you guys thinking straight?
여러분, 똑바로 생각하고 계시나요?
We're Section E.
우리는 섹션 E입니다.
Do you really think that'll work? Good lord.
정말 그렇게 생각하시나요? 그게 효과가 있겠어? 좋은 영주님.
That makes sense.
말이 되네요.
Well that's something else.
글쎄, 그것은 다른 것입니다.
You look genuinely concerned for Jay-jay.
당신은 진심으로 보입니다 제이제이가 걱정된다.
Hey!
여기요!
- Dumbass! - Bad joke.
- 멍청아! - 나쁜 농담.
Just kidding. It was a joke, dude.
농담이에요. 농담이었어, 친구.
Can't you take a joke?
농담을 할 수 없나요?
Oh? What now?
오? 지금은 무엇입니까?
Now...
이제...
we move to Plan X.
우리는 플랜 X로 이동합니다.
Let's go!
갑시다!
That's in English, guys. You got nothing on me.
그건 영어에요, 여러분. 당신은 나에 대해 아무것도 없어.
This is fun.
재미있습니다.
Hold on...
잠깐만요...
Where is Yuri, by the way?
그런데 유리는 어디에 있나요?
- Why isn't he here? - Yeah, you're right.
- 그 사람은 왜 여기 없나요? - 네, 당신 말이 맞아요.
Where is he?
그는 어디에 있나요?
His hair is stark red and yet you can't find him?
그의 머리카락은 새빨갛지만, 그 사람 못 찾나요?
He looks like a rooster for god's sake!
그는 수탉처럼 보인다 제발!
He's gone missing again.
그 사람 또 실종됐어요
- Maybe he's in their shop. - You asked about it, didn't you? Are you stupid?
- 어쩌면 그 사람 가게에 있을지도 모르죠. - 당신이 물어봤잖아요, 그렇죠? 당신은 바보입니까?
I'll beat your ass.
내가 당신 엉덩이를 때릴 것이다.
Let's do one game?
한 게임 해볼까요?
Huh? One more game?
뭐? 한 게임 더?
Let's go.
갑시다.
- I don't really feel like it. - Another one?
- 별로 그럴 기분이 아니야. - 또 하나?
All of you are soft.
여러분 모두 부드럽습니다.
- Let me just get my things. - Wow...
- 내 물건만 가져오도록 할게요. - 와...
Game, let's go!
게임, 가자!
- But I was game. - Did you hear that?
- 하지만 난 장난이었어. - 들었어?
- Soft. - Let's play, guys.
- 부드러운. - 놀자 얘들아.
What does he mean?
그 말은 무슨 뜻인가요?
You asshole.
이 멍청아.
When you said you're gonna take me home, I thought you had a car.
당신이 나를 집에 데려다 주겠다고 말했을 때, 나는 당신이 차를 가지고 있다고 생각했습니다.
Hey! Don't hold me there! I'm getting ticklish!
여기요! 나를 거기에 가두지 마세요! 간지러워지네요!
- What's the problem?! The backseat is tiny! - Just grab onto something else! Not there!
- 뭐가 문제야?! 뒷좌석은 좁습니다! - 그냥 다른 걸 잡으세요! 거기가 아니야!
Huh?!
뭐?!
Here!
여기!
Not there! On my shoulders! Hold on to my shoulders!
거기가 아니야! 내 어깨에! 내 어깨를 잡아라!
On your shoulders?
어깨에?
- On my shoulders! - [Jay-jay screams]
- 내 어깨에! - [제이제이가 비명을 지른다]
- Jay, are you okay? - Ouch...
- 제이, 괜찮아? - 아야...
Oh shit, you got hurt!
아 젠장, 다쳤어!
Are you okay, Jay?
괜찮아, 제이?
Just a moment. [Jay-jay flinches]
잠시만요. [제이제이가 움찔함]
- Slow down! - You didn't listen to me!
- 천천히 하세요! - 내 말을 안 들었잖아!
Be gentle with it!
부드럽게 대하세요!
Come on, are you okay?
어서, 괜찮아?
- This is your fault. - Hop in. Let's just go.
- 이건 당신 잘못이에요. - 타세요. 그냥 가죠.
Let's just walk from here.
여기서부터는 그냥 걸어가자.
No, ride the bike.
아니요, 자전거를 타세요.
What if we fall again?!
또 넘어지면 어쩌지?!
You're not gonna fall. Just hop on.
당신은 넘어지지 않을 것입니다. 그냥 타세요.
So pushy.
너무 강압적이에요.
You're so stubborn. You can't stay still.
당신은 너무 고집스럽군요. 가만히 있을 수는 없어요.
- It's you who's stubborn. - No, it's you.
- 고집이 센 건 바로 당신이에요. - 아니, 당신이에요.
You are!
당신은!
Am I the one driving?!
내가 운전하는 거야?!
Just get on it!
그냥 타세요!
My helmet!
내 헬멧!
[Jay-jay groans]
[제이제이가 신음함]
You're so slow. Just get on!
당신은 너무 느리다. 그냥 타세요!
Can't you wait?
기다릴 수 없나요?
You good?
잘 지내요?
Yeah.
응.
You're gonna walk? Our house is still far from here.
걸어갈 건가요? 우리 집은 여기서 아직 멀다.
I can handle it, Jay. Just stay still.
난 감당할 수 있어, 제이. 그냥 가만히 있어라.
Alright then.
그럼요.
Yeah.
응.
Are you okay, Jay?
괜찮아, 제이?
I should be asking you that.
나는 당신에게 그것을 물어봐야합니다.
I told you I can walk.
걸을 수 있다고 말했어요.
Just don't argue anymore, Jay. Please.
그냥 논쟁하지 마세요 더 이상, 제이. 제발.
Hey. It's here!
여기요. 여기 있어요!
Here?
여기?
- Yeah. Here. - Wait...
- 응. 여기. - 잠깐...
Just stay still, alright?
그냥 가만히 있어, 알았지?
Hold on...
잠깐만요...
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Jay, don't be stubborn. You can't even walk right now.
제이, 고집 부리지 마세요. 지금은 걸을 수도 없습니다.
Jay-jay!
제이제이!
Jay...
제이...
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
I'm sorry. I got her injured.
죄송합니다. 나는 그녀를 부상당하게 만들었다.
Get down from there.
거기서 내려오세요.
It's embarrassing to your companion.
동반자에게는 당혹스럽습니다.
But Grandma, he insists on carrying me.
그런데 할머니, 그 사람이 저를 안고 가겠다고 하더군요.
Grandma, do you have a first-aid kit?
할머니, 있어요? 구급상자?
Of course we do. Come on inside.
물론 그렇습니다. 안으로 들어가세요.
Hurry up. Go on.
서둘러요. 계속하세요.
Your wound needs to be treated.
상처를 치료해야 합니다.
Sorry...
미안...
Quickly!
빠르게!
You can put me down here.
나를 여기 내려놓으시면 됩니다.
Come on. Here. Over here.
어서 해봐요. 여기. 여기요.
What on Earth happened to you?
도대체 무슨 일이 일어난 걸까요?
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Put me down here.
나를 여기 내려 놓으십시오.
- Sorry, sorry. - There, there, there.
- 미안해요, 미안해요. - 저기, 저기, 저기.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- 여기요. - 감사합니다.
- I'll do it. - Just let me, Jay.
- 내가 할게요. - 그냥 놔두세요, 제이.
Where are you hurting?
어디 아프세요?
[Grandma reacts]
[할머니 반응]
He's gonna put an ointment. That would sting.
연고를 바르실 거예요. 그러면 따가울 것입니다.
[Jay-jay flinches]
[제이제이가 움찔함]
Sorry, Jay. Sorry...
미안해, 제이. 미안...
Just a little more, Jay.
조금만 더, 제이.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
I have no idea.
나는 모른다.
Here it goes, Jay.
간다, 제이.
I'll cover your wound.
당신의 상처를 덮어줄게요.
Hold on for a little longer.
조금만 더 기다려주세요.
There.
거기.
It's done, Jay.
다 됐어, 제이.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
This should do it.
이렇게 하면 됩니다.
Is he your boyfriend?
그 사람이 네 남자친구야?
He's not her boyfriend.
그는 그녀의 남자친구가 아닙니다.
Are you courting her?
당신은 그녀에게 구애하고 있나요?
No, Grandma.
아니, 할머니.
He's my classmate.
그 사람은 내 동급생이에요.
Yes.
예.
Oohh... classmate.
아... 동급생.
Alright. Thank you very much for your help.
괜찮은. 도움을 주셔서 대단히 감사합니다.
I'm done using this too. Thank you.
저도 이것으로 사용이 끝났습니다. 감사합니다.
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
It's none of your business.
그것은 당신의 사업이 아닙니다.
Grandma, my apologies. I'll get going now.
할머니, 죄송해요. 이제 가겠습니다.
Wait. Do not go yet.
기다리다. 아직 가지 마세요.
Have dinner with us.
우리와 함께 저녁을 먹어요.
Granda, just let him leave.
할아버지, 그냥 떠나게 해주세요.
He's not welcome in this house.
그는 이 집에서 환영받지 못합니다.
Aries...
양자리...
Grandma?
할머니?
[Grandma scoffs]
[할머니가 비웃는다]
[Aries flinches in pain]
[양자리는 고통에 움찔한다]
Ouch!
아야!
That's not even my full strength.
그건 내 힘조차 전부가 아니야.
[Grandma chuckles]
[할머니가 웃는다]
When did you become disrespectful?
언제부터 무례하게 됐나요?
We don't treat our guests that way.
우리는 손님을 그런 식으로 대하지 않습니다.
You understand?
이해하셨나요?
He's a guest.
그는 손님입니다.
Don't leave yet.
아직 떠나지 마세요.
Please have dinner here.
여기서 저녁을 드세요.
Rosario!
로사리오!
Ruth!
룻!
Oh, dear.
이런.
You two are so slow! Watching a TV drama again?
너희 둘은 너무 느리다! 또 드라마를 볼까?
Set the table. We're gonna have dinner.
테이블을 설정합니다. 우리는 저녁을 먹을 거예요.
You, Jay-jay.
너, 제이제이.
Yes?
예?
- Change clothes. - Oh, alright.
- 옷을 갈아입으세요. - 아, 알았어.
Aren't you embarrassed in front of your friend?
부끄럽지 않나요? 친구 앞에서?
- Go on. Fix yourself. - Yes, Grandma.
- 계속하세요. 스스로 고치세요. - 네, 할머니.
[Jay-jay reacts in pain]
[제이제이가 고통스러워하며 반응함]
Go on, boy.
계속해라, 얘야.
You go ahead to the dining room. I'll help her.
너는 앞으로 가 식당. 내가 그녀를 도와줄게.
- Oh, okay. - Okay.
- 아, 그래요. - 좋아요.
Grandma, let's go.
할머니, 가세요.
- Let's eat.
- 먹자.
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Slowly.
느리게.
Just because your Aunt Gemma isn't around, you have the nerve to bring a boy here.
단지 젬마 이모가 주변에 없기 때문에 당신은 소년을 여기로 데려올 용기가 있습니다.
It's not like that. He's just a classmate.
그렇지 않습니다. 그는 단지 동급생입니다.
After what happened to your ex, you have the nerve to flirt again?
전 애인에게 일어난 일 이후, 또 바람을 피울 용기가 있어?
It's not like that.
그렇지 않습니다.
Did you know he woke up?
그 사람이 깨어난 걸 알고 있었나요?
And he was looking for you.
그리고 그는 당신을 찾고있었습니다.
I'm leaving. You better behave yourself.
나는 떠난다. 스스로 행동하는 것이 좋습니다.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Move now.
지금 움직여라.
Slowly.
느리게.
[Jay-jay reacts in pain]
[제이제이가 고통스러워하며 반응함]
Who are your parents again, Yuri?
유리야, 네 부모님은 누구야?
Yumori and Yakito Hanamitchi.
유모리와 하나미치 야키토.
Oh, Japanese.
아, 일본인.
Grandma.
할머니.
He's the grandson of Yuori Hanamitchi.
하나미치 유오리의 손자.
The owner of the company we're closing a deal with.
회사의 소유자 우리는 거래를 마무리하고 있습니다.
Ahh, I see.
아, 그렇군요.
[In Japanese] Good evening.
[일본어] 안녕하세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
You know how to speak Japanese?
일본어 할 줄 아세요?
I'm just imitating the words.
나는 단지 말을 흉내내는 것뿐입니다.
[Yuri chuckles]
[유리가 웃는다]
How is your grandfather now?
할아버지는 지금 어떤가요?
He's currently in Japan.
그는 현재 일본에 있습니다.
- After you eat, tell him to go home. - Wait a minute…
- 식사 후에는 집에 가라고 하세요. - 잠깐만요…
have you been to Japan?
일본에 가본 적이 있나요?
- After you eat, tell him to go home! - Not yet.
- 식사 후에는 집에 가라고 하세요! - 아직 아님.
Not yet?
아직 아님?
- You should go to Japan. - I'm planning to.
- 일본에 가셔야 해요. - 그럴 예정이에요.
- I will. - My most favorite is there.
- 그럴게요. - 내가 가장 좋아하는 것이 거기 있다.
- If you don't want that, I'll have it. - It's not yucky.
- 원치 않으시면 제가 갖겠습니다. - 별거 아니예요.
- But it's sukiyaki. - What these?
- 그런데 스키야키예요. - 이게 뭐야?
Sure!
확신하는!
Alright, let's continue eating.
알았어, 계속 먹자.
You can have the rest of it.
나머지는 가져가시면 됩니다.
Jay-jay.
제이제이.
You don't seem too keen on vegetables.
당신은 야채를 별로 좋아하지 않는 것 같아요.
You should train yourself to eat them.
먹을 수 있도록 훈련해야 합니다.
Oh, it's not that. It's Yuri's favorite.
아, 그게 아니고요. 유리가 가장 좋아하는 것입니다.
- Oh, wow. Is that so? - That's why I'm giving it to him.
- 아, 와. 그렇습니까? - 그래서 내가 그 사람에게 주는 거야.
- It's his favorite. - I think I'm beginning to smell something.
- 그가 가장 좋아하는 것이에요. - 뭔가 냄새가 나기 시작한 것 같아요.
Something in the ways.
뭔가 방해가 됩니다.
Of you two...
너희 둘 중...
[Grandma chuckles]
[할머니가 웃는다]
Alright, go on…
좋아, 계속해...
Love…
사랑…
- Give me your potatoes. - You want these?
- 감자를 주세요. - 이걸 원해요?
Give them all to me.
나에게 모두 주세요.
Oh, so it's potatoes you like?
아, 그럼 감자를 좋아하시나요?
Potatoes, potatoes…
감자, 감자…
These beans are delicious.
이 콩은 맛있어요.
- These are crunchy beans, aren't they? - The beans are delicious.
- 이거 바삭바삭한 콩이군요, 그렇죠? - 콩이 맛있어요.
What about the potatoes? There's lots of them.
감자는 어때요? 그것들이 많이 있습니다.
It's tasty, Grandma.
맛있어요, 할머니.
Oh, really?
오, 진짜?
But you know what happens to you?
하지만 당신에게 무슨 일이 일어나는지 아시나요?
After you take so many potatoes and camote?
감자와 카모테를 그렇게 많이 먹은 후에요?
What?
무엇?
Walk gently.
부드럽게 걸어보세요.
[Jay-jay grunts]
[제이제이가 투덜거린다]
There. It looks like you can walk better now.
거기. 할 수 있을 것 같습니다 이제 좀 더 잘 걸어보세요.
Thank you. Even though this was all your fault.
감사합니다. 그래도 이건 다 네 잘못이야.
Tss.
쯧쯧.
[Yuri exhales deeply]
[유리가 깊게 숨을 내쉰다]
Thanks, too.
고마워요.
Please tell them I'm thankful for the dinner.
그들에게 내가 그렇다고 말해주세요 저녁 식사 감사합니다.
Alright. Take care.
괜찮은. 잘 지내세요.
I'll go ahead.
나는 계속할 것이다.
Yuri!
유리!
Have lunch with me and Ci-N sometimes.
나랑 점심 먹자 때로는 Ci-N도 있습니다.
Sure.
확신하는.
- Take care. - Okay, Jay.
- 잘 지내세요. - 알았어, 제이.
Get some rest.
좀 쉬세요.
Good night.
안녕히 주무세요.
Bye!
안녕!
Oh!
오!
I forgot about that asshole's message.
그 새끼의 메시지를 잊어버렸어요.
"I have another plan."
"다른 계획이 있어요."
What could that be?
그게 무엇일까요?
[Section E boys chattering loudly]
[시끄럽게 떠들고 있는 섹션 E 소년들]
Denzel!
덴젤!
Hey, Jay!
안녕, 제이!
What's happening there?
무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Tell me what's happening inside.
안에서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 말해주세요.
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
Let me see!
어디 보자!
I will punch you in the face if you don't let me through!
난 네 얼굴에 주먹을 날릴 거야 나를 통과시키지 않으면!
You can't!
당신은 할 수 없습니다!
Stop it!
그만해요!
Look! There's food over there.
바라보다! 저기 음식이 있어요.
- Where?! - Right there!
- 어디?! - 바로 거기!
Jay, you can't come inside!
제이, 안에 들어오면 안돼!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
여기요! 도대체 뭐하는 거야?!
We're letting them "talk."
우리는 그들이 "대화"하도록 놔두고 있습니다.
Talk about what?
무슨 얘기?
Because of what they did to Ci-N!
그들이 Ci-N에게 한 짓 때문이에요!
Ci-N! Will you quit it?!
Ci-N! 그만둘래?!
Not because you're hurting them, they will tell the truth!
당신이 그들에게 상처를 주기 때문이 아닙니다. 그들은 진실을 말할 것이다!
They could lie even more because they're scared of what you'll do to them.
그들은 더 많은 거짓말을 할 수 있습니다. 그들은 당신이 그들에게 무슨 짓을 할지 두려워합니다.
This is not the right way.
이것은 올바른 방법이 아닙니다.
Will you let her go, please?
그녀를 보내주시겠어요?
Why are you meddling?
왜 간섭하는 거야?
Aren't you scared of getting caught?! How about the rest of you?!
들킬까 두렵지 않으신가요?! 나머지 분들은 어떻습니까?!
And aren't you one strike away from expulsion?
그리고 당신은 원스트라이크 아닌가요? 퇴학을 앞두고?
Look at him. His eyes are already swollen!
그를보세요. 그의 눈 벌써 부어있어!
We're interrogating him!
우리는 그를 심문하고 있습니다!
And what if they don't know anything?
그리고 그들이 아무것도 모른다면?
Fine. We're spilling the truth.
괜찮은. 우리는 진실을 흘리고 있습니다.
There you go.
됐어요.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
[Imelda stuttering]
[이멜다 말더듬]
- What? Tell us! - See?
- 무엇? 우리에게 말해주세요! - 보다?
Say it, quickly!
빨리 말해!
I can't say it.
나는 그것을 말할 수 없다.
My God, why can't you just spill it?
맙소사, 왜 그냥 흘리면 안 되나요?
Shoot!
사격!
You know what...
그거 알아요...
Hey, hey, hey!
헤이, 헤이, 헤이!
- I thought violence is not the right way? - Hey, relax.
- 폭력은 옳지 않은 방법이라고 생각했나요? - 이봐, 진정해.
She's getting on my nerves. Why can't she just say it?
그녀가 내 신경을 거슬리게 하고 있어요. 왜 그녀는 그것을 말할 수 없습니까?
See, we told you so.
보세요, 우리는 그렇게 말했습니다.
You're not gonna say it?
말하지 않을 건가요?
Hold her again.
그녀를 다시 잡아라.
Come here.
이리 오세요.
[Imelda cries]
[이멜다가 울다]
My turn.
내 차례.
Don't!
하지 않다!
I'm begging you!
부탁해요!
Keifer!
키퍼!
They just need to say it.
그들은 단지 그것을 말하기만 하면 됩니다.
Have mercy! Let my boyfriend go!
자비를 베푸소서! 내 남자 친구를 보내주세요!
You don't wanna talk?
얘기하고 싶지 않아?
Okay.
좋아요.
We're gonna say it!
우리는 그것을 말할 것입니다!
We were instructed to do it.
우리는 그렇게 하라는 지시를 받았습니다.
She promised lots of things. That's why we did it.
그녀는 많은 것을 약속했습니다. 그것이 우리가 그렇게 한 이유입니다.
Who instructed you?
누가 지시했나요?
I really can't tell you...
정말 말할 수가 없어요...
Is that all good?
그게 다 좋은가요?
Yeah, that's enough.
응, 그거면 충분해.
I caught her confession on video.
그녀의 고백을 영상으로 담아봤습니다.
That's the only thing that matters, right?
중요한 건 그것뿐이지, 그렇지?
Check it.
확인해보세요.
Thank you, Rakki.
고마워요, 라키.
[Section E boys teasing]
[섹션 E 남자들이 놀리는 중]
Was this the plan you were talking about?
이것이 당신이 말했던 계획이었나요?
Yeah.
응.
And even if it's against my nature to cooperate with Section E…
그리고 그것이 내 본성에 어긋나더라도 섹션 E와 협력하기 위해…
I volunteered so that I can help you, Jay.
나는 당신을 돕기 위해 자원했습니다, 제이.
You really wanted to help Jay-jay, not me?
당신은 정말로 원했어요 내가 말고 Jay-jay를 도와주세요?
[Section E boys teasing]
[섹션 E 남자들이 놀리는 중]
You're so cringey.
너 정말 오싹하다.
Let me have a look.
좀 보도록 할게요.
Drix, get the camera.
드릭스, 카메라 가져와
Okay, leave it to me.
좋아요, 나에게 맡겨주세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Somebody get this guy to the clinic.
누가 이 사람을 진료소로 데려가세요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
- Rakki… - Come with us.
- 라키… - 우리와 함께 가자.
Thank you for helping.
도와주셔서 감사합니다.
That's nothing.
그건 아무것도 아닙니다.
And I really wanted to help Ci-N too.
그리고 저도 Ci-N을 꼭 돕고 싶었어요.
I wasn't here when that incident happened.
그 사건이 일어났을 때 나는 여기에 없었습니다.
But what about you?
하지만 당신은 어떻습니까?
I'm sure Aries and his friends will hear about this.
나는 양자리와 그의 친구들은 이 소식을 듣게 될 것입니다.
We believe one of them plotted this against Ci-N.
우리는 그 중 하나를 믿습니다 Ci-N을 상대로 이것을 계획했습니다.
I guess it's for the best.
나는 그것이 최선이라고 생각합니다.
I'm just forcing myself to befriend them.
나는 단지 그들과 친구가 되라고 강요하고 있습니다.
Lately, I realized their bad attitude is rubbing off on me.
최근에 나는 그들의 나쁜 점을 깨달았습니다. 태도가 나에게 영향을 미치고 있습니다.
Good thing my classmates are all good people. They always tell me the truth.
다행이다 우리 반 친구들은 다 착해 사람들. 그들은 항상 나에게 진실을 말합니다.
Aren't you afraid of what they can do to you?
두렵지 않나요? 그 사람들이 너한테 무슨 짓을 할 수 있어?
No, silly. I can surely handle it.
아니, 바보야. 나는 확실히 그것을 처리할 수 있습니다.
I'm Rakki, after all.
결국 나는 Rakki입니다.
I swear. You don't need to worry.
맹세해요. 걱정할 필요가 없습니다.
If they ever do anything to you…
만약 그들이 당신에게 무슨 짓을 했다면...
I'll deal with them myself.
내가 직접 처리하겠습니다.
I'll hold you to that.
나는 당신을 붙잡을 것입니다.
Revenge without violence.
폭력 없이 복수하세요.
I'm a changed woman.
나는 변화된 여자입니다.
Jay-jay, just make sure of it.
제이제이, 꼭 확인해 보세요.
I promise!
약속해요!
- I truly am changed! - I'm turning a new leaf.
- 정말 변했어요! - 새 출발을 하고 있어요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
I got you, bro.
알았어, 형.
Hey, dude, are you okay?
안녕 친구, 괜찮아?
Easy.
쉬운.
[Edrix grunting]
[에드릭스 투덜거림]
You type so fast.
당신은 너무 빨리 입력합니다.
And... all...
그리고... 모두...
Done.
완료.
You can all open your FaceGrams.
모두 FaceGram을 열 수 있습니다.
It's up. Check it!
다 됐다. 확인해보세요!
[Section E Boys reacting]
[섹션 E 소년 반응]
We were instructed to do it.
우리는 그렇게 하라는 지시를 받았습니다.
- Bro, so cool! - All is in order now!
- 형, 정말 멋지네요! - 이제 모든 것이 정리되었습니다!
Ci-N!
Ci-N!
[Section E boys cheering]
[섹션 E 소년들의 응원]
Wait, wait. Why did you post it using Freya's account?
잠깐만요. 왜 글을 올렸지? 프레야의 계정을 사용하는 건가요?
Is this really hers?
이게 정말 그녀의 것인가요?
Of course.
물론.
Freya's account hacked by none other than...
프레야의 계정 해킹당한 사람은 다름 아닌...
[drum roll]
[드럼 롤]
Edrix... Knight.
에드릭스... 기사님.
[Section E boys laughing]
[섹션 E 웃는 남자들]
Let's make a bet!
내기하자!
I'm sure Freya's fuming with anger.
프레야가 화를 내고 있는 게 틀림없어요.
[Section E boys laughing]
[섹션 E 웃는 남자들]
You owe me again.
당신은 나에게 또 빚을 졌어요.
That's two points for me now.
이제 나에게는 두 가지 포인트가 있습니다.
Wow.
우와.
What if you got caught? All of you will be suspended.
잡히면 어떡하지? 여러분 모두 정지 처분을 받게 됩니다.
How about a thank you?
감사 인사는 어떻습니까?
That's right. Say thanks to Keifer.
좋아요. Keifer에게 감사 인사를 전하세요.
You're too much, Jay.
넌 너무 과해, 제이.
[Section E teasing Jay-jay]
[제이제이를 놀리는 섹션 E]
- Don't be too stingy. - Just one thank you.
- 너무 인색하지 마세요. - 한 번만 감사드립니다.
Wait! You're all so loud! Why are you pressuring me?
기다리다! 다들 너무 시끄러워요! 왜 나에게 압력을 가하는 거죠?
Keifer.
키퍼.
Let me go first.
나 먼저 가보자.
[Ci-N clears throat]
[Ci-N이 목을 가다듬는다]
Thank you.
감사합니다.
[Section E boys laughing]
[섹션 E 웃는 남자들]
So...
그럼...
your turn.
당신 차례입니다.
You're so good! Alright!
당신은 정말 좋아요! 괜찮은!
- Alright. - You're okay now?
- 괜찮은. - 이제 괜찮아요?
What the fuck?!
도대체 뭐야?!
Freya! Language!
프레야! 언어!
Shut up!
입 다물어!
OMG.
어머나.
Is this your FaceGram account?
이것이 당신의 FaceGram 계정입니까?
Well, duh? Are you dumb? Hell yeah, it's mine.
응? 당신은 바보입니까? 그래, 그건 내 거야.
You can clearly see my name on it!
거기에 내 이름이 확실히 보이네요!
There's my face on the DP. It's so, so pretty.
DP에 내 얼굴이 있어요. 정말 너무 예뻐요.
And then someone will post trash like this?!
그리고 누군가 이런 쓰레기를 게시할 것인가?!
My gosh. Who did this?!
맙소사. 누가 그랬어?!
Maybe it was you!
아마도 당신이었을 거예요!
- Yeah. - You're overacting
- 응. - 지나치게 행동하고 있어
I know you have my password on your phone.
나는 당신이 내 것을 가지고 있다는 것을 압니다 휴대전화의 비밀번호.
I didn't touch your phone.
난 네 전화기를 만지지 않았어.
I know you're obsessed with me since Day 1. Just admit it, Kiko!
당신이 첫날부터 나에게 집착했다는 걸 알아요. 그냥 인정해, 키코!
You wish.
당신은 원합니다.
You, come with me. Over here.
당신은 나와 함께 가세요. 여기요.
Hey, you!
이봐, 너!
Hey!
여기요!
Come! It was probably you, huh?! What are you doing here?!
오다! 아마 당신이었겠죠?! 여기서 뭐하는거야?!
We were instructed to do it.
우리는 그렇게 하라는 지시를 받았습니다.
What's wrong, babe?
무슨 일이야?
That's why we did it.
그것이 우리가 그렇게 한 이유입니다.
Open it.
열어보세요.
Show me your phone.
휴대폰을 보여주세요.
I wanna eat right now. I'm so hungry!
지금 당장 먹고 싶어요. 너무 배가 고파요!
[Freya interrogating other students]
[다른 학생들을 심문하는 프레야]
Just let them be, babe.
그냥 그렇게 놔둬, 자기야.
It would be too obvious if we do something.
우리가 뭔가를 하면 너무 뻔할 것 같아요.
What now?
지금은 무엇입니까?
Pay what you owe.
당신이 빚진 것을 지불하십시오.
Huh?
뭐?
Oh, that.
아, 그거요.
I still have nothing. Sorry.
나는 아직 아무것도 가지고 있지 않습니다. 죄송합니다.
When are you going to pay me?
언제 지불할 예정인가요?
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
Didn't say thank you. Didn't even pay.
고맙다는 말은 안 했어요. 심지어 지불하지도 않았습니다.
I get it.
알겠습니다.
How about…
어때요...
you pay me with something else?
나한테 다른 걸 지불하는 거야?
You don't want to?
당신은 원하지 않습니까?
Asshole!
항문!
I'm just messing with you!
난 그냥 너랑 장난하는 거야!
Asshole.
항문.
Just pay me with food.
그냥 음식값으로 갚으세요.
Food?
음식?
I want one. Bring food for me as well.
나는 하나를 원한다. 나를 위한 음식도 가져오세요.
Until when?
언제까지?
Until graduation.
졸업까지.
Tough luck.
행운을 빕니다.
You owe me twenty five thousand. I'm practically getting nothing back.
당신은 나에게 2만 5천 빚을 졌습니다. 나는 사실상 아무것도 돌려받지 못하고 있습니다.
Okay. It's 150 per lunch box.
좋아요. 도시락 하나당 150원이에요.
50.
50.
150.
150.
- 60. - 150!
- 60. - 150!
You're overpricing!
가격이 너무 비싸요!
Prices of ingredients are extremely high!
재료 가격이 엄청나게 높습니다!
Hey!
여기요!
Let's just start today?
오늘부터 시작해볼까요?
So stubborn!
너무 고집이 세다!
Oh. I didn't know you were there.
오. 나는 당신이 거기에 있는지 몰랐습니다.
You told me, didn't you?
당신이 말했지요, 그렇죠?
Told you what?
뭐라고 말했어?
Lunch.
점심.
Oh yeah! Those two are waiting for us.
아 그래! 그 두 사람이 우리를 기다리고 있어요.
Let's go.
가자.
Finally, Jay, you're here. We've been here forever.
드디어 제이, 당신이 왔네요. 우리는 영원히 여기에 있었습니다.
What took you so long?
왜 그렇게 오래 걸렸나요?
Look, my arms are getting skinnier...
봐봐 내 팔이 점점 가늘어지고 있어...
Oh?
오?
Hey.
여기요.
Why are you here, Yuri?
왜 여기 있어, 유리?
He's gonna eat lunch with us.
그 사람은 우리와 함께 점심을 먹을 거예요.
Grab a chair. Sit here.
의자를 잡아라. 여기 앉으세요.
Ouch!
아야!
You guys really hang out here?
너희들 정말 여기서 놀고 있는 거야?
Where is Calix, by the way?
그런데 Calix는 어디에 있나요?
Calix?
칼릭스?
He's with Mica in the other room.
그는 다른 방에 미카와 함께 있어요.
Flirting.
유혹.
Let them be. They give me butterflies. They only got back together recently, anyway.
그렇게 놔두세요. 그들은 나에게 나비를 준다. 그들은 어쨌든 최근에야 다시 모였지.
Oh. Here's your food.
오. 여기 음식이 있습니다.
Cool!
시원한!
We're so famished!
우리는 너무 배고프다!
Thank you, Jay.
고마워요, 제이.
We've been here for a long time.
우리는 오랫동안 여기에 있었습니다.
[Jay-jay sighs]
[제이제이가 한숨을 쉬다]
[Ci-N and David happily chattering]
[Ci-N과 David가 즐겁게 수다를 떨고 있음]
What's this?
이건 뭐죠?
Is this mine?
이거 내꺼야?
I'm just asking you to open it.
그냥 열어달라는 거에요.
I'm joking. It's really yours.
농담이에요. 그것은 정말로 당신 것입니다.
I felt sorry for you when Keifer stole your food.
나는 당신에게 미안하다고 느꼈다 Keifer가 음식을 훔쳤을 때.
Really? Is this for real?
정말? 이게 진짜인가요?
[Ci-N and David sighs in contentment]
[Ci-N과 David가 만족스러운 한숨을 쉬었습니다.]
Say "ahh."
"아아"라고 말해보세요.
"Ahh."
"아아."
- Bigger. - Ah!
- 더 커요. - 아!
[Yuri chuckles]
[유리가 웃는다]
What the hell. It's too big.
도대체 뭐지? 너무 크다.
It's so delicious!
너무 맛있어요!
Here, eat up.
자, 먹어보세요.
It's good!
좋다!
Hey, you have your own food.
이봐요, 당신만의 음식이 있어요.
Selfish.
이기적인.
Just kidding.
농담이에요.
Good food can really make your day, don't you think?
좋은 음식은 정말 당신의 하루를 즐겁게 해줄 수 있고, 그렇지 않은 것 같나요?
Here, for the glutton.
여기, 대식가를 위한 것입니다.
This is so delicious!
정말 맛있어요!
This is my favorite!
이것은 내가 가장 좋아하는 것입니다!
You know what, I'll just use my hands.
그거 알아요, 그냥 손을 쓰겠습니다.
So yummy.
정말 맛있어요.
Eating can really make one happy, don't you think?
먹으면 정말 만들 수 있다 행복할 것 같지 않나요?
But we would be so much happier if we're eating at the canteen.
하지만 우리는 훨씬 더 행복할 거예요 우리가 구내식당에서 식사를 하고 있다면요.
If only we could.
우리가 할 수만 있다면.
- Jay. - Hmm?
- 제이. - 흠?
Whose side will you be on if ever…
만약에 당신은 누구의 편에 설 것인가…
Aries and Keifer fight again?
양자리와 케이퍼가 또 싸운다?
I don't know. I'm torn.
모르겠습니다. 나는 찢어졌다.
You don't need to choose.
선택할 필요가 없습니다.
You've been caught in our mess for far too long.
당신은 사로잡혔어요 우리의 혼란은 너무 오랫동안 지속되었습니다.
No matter who you side with, you'll still end up getting hurt.
당신이 누구의 편에 서든 상관없습니다. 당신은 여전히 ​​상처를 입을 것입니다.
How can you say?
어떻게 말할 수 있습니까?
You're part of Section E. And Aries is your family.
당신은 섹션 E의 일부입니다. 그리고 양자리는 당신의 가족입니다.
You think you won't get involved?
당신은 관여하지 않을 것 같아요?
Go on, eat up.
어서 먹어라.
Eat up.
먹어라.
Do you want sushi?
초밥을 원하시나요?
- You took my food. Give it back. - Kidding, this is mine.
- 당신은 내 음식을 가져갔습니다. 돌려주세요. - 농담이야, 이건 내꺼야.
Give it to me.
나에게 주세요.
Damn that asshole. He made my life harder.
젠장, 그 새끼야. 그는 내 인생을 더 힘들게 만들었어요.
And of all times, my bike broke down too. Such a hassle!
그리고 언제나 내 자전거는 역시 무너졌습니다. 정말 번거로운 일이군요!
Hi.
안녕.
It's you again?
또 당신이에요?
Going to school?
학교에 가나요?
Mm.
Mm.
You have a lot on your hands.
당신의 손에는 많은 것이 있습니다.
I'm heading out. I can give you a ride.
나는 밖으로 향하고있다. 제가 태워드릴 수 있어요.
No need. It's alright.
필요하지 않습니다. 괜찮아요.
Are you sure? I'm heading the same way.
확실합니까? 나도 같은 방향으로 가고 있어요.
You look like you're struggling.
당신은 어려움을 겪고 있는 것처럼 보입니다.
No, I'm alright. Go.
아니요, 저는 괜찮아요. 가다.
Okay.
좋아요.
That was weird.
이상했어요.
Are you deaf?
당신은 귀머거리입니까?
I've been calling you.
나는 당신에게 전화를 걸었습니다.
I thought it's for someone else.
다른 사람을 위한 거라고 생각했어요.
Get in. I'm taking you to school.
타세요. 내가 당신을 학교에 데려다 줄 거에요.
Wow...
와...
Are you taking me to school because you don't have a bike to steal?
나 때문에 학교에 데려가는 거야? 훔칠 자전거 없나요?
Get it.
그것을 얻으십시오.
Okay.
좋아요.
If you insist.
당신이 주장한다면.
So cool.
정말 멋지다.
[Jay-jay grunts in pain]
[제이제이가 고통스러워 신음함]
My body aches all over.
온몸이 아프다.
You know, good thing you gave me a ride.
있잖아, 좋은 일이야 당신은 나를 태워주었습니다.
Why are you in our village again?
왜 또 우리 마을에 왔어?
Ah... I went somewhere nearby.
아... 근처에 갔었어요.
At this early hour?
이 이른 시간에?
Yeah.
응.
Lucky for me.
나에게는 행운이다.
What's in there? You look so worn out.
거기에 무엇이 있습니까? 당신은 너무 지쳐 보이는군요.
These are lunch boxes I share with David, Ci-N, and Keifer the asshole.
이건 내가 함께 나눠먹는 도시락이야 David, Ci-N, Keifer는 멍청한 놈입니다.
Why are you packing lunch for Keifer too?
왜 짐을 싸는 거야? Keifer 점심도요?
- Payment— - Because she wants to.
- 결제— - 그녀가 원하기 때문이죠.
That's not true! This is payment for my debt!
그것은 사실이 아닙니다! 이건 내 빚에 대한 갚는 일이야!
Debt?
빚?
I'll explain later.
나중에 설명하겠습니다.
Hey!
여기요!
Give that back! I don't want to hear an earful from you!
돌려줘! 나는 원하지 않는다 당신의 말을 잘 들어보세요!
Give it to me!
나에게 줘!
I said, give it back!
내가 말했잖아, 돌려줘!
- Huh? - Give it back now!
- 뭐? - 당장 돌려줘!
Give it back!
돌려줘!
You're so annoying!
당신은 정말 짜증나!
Give it back, Keifer! Stop treating me like a kid!
돌려줘, 키퍼! 나를 어린애 취급하지 마세요!
My arms are getting tired.
팔이 점점 피곤해지고 있어요.
I'm getting tired!
피곤해요!
There.
거기.
Look what you did.
당신이 무슨 짓을했는지보세요.
Give it to me.
나에게 주세요.
Give us some!
우리에게 좀 주세요!
- Hey! That's mine! - Share this with us!
- 여기요! 그건 내 꺼야! - 이것을 우리와 공유해보세요!
- Give us some too! - Take it here!
- 우리도 좀 주세요! - 여기로 가져가세요!
[Section E boys clamoring]
[섹션 E의 소년들의 아우성]
It's all your fault!
다 네 잘못이야!
Class.
수업.
Settle down.
진정하세요.
Go back to your seats.
자리로 돌아가세요.
Let's talk about the festival.
축제에 대해 이야기해보자.
Aren't we far ahead of time? Why are we discussing it this early?
우리는 훨씬 앞서 있지 않은가? 왜 이렇게 일찍 논의하는 걸까요?
There is a chance that it will be held earlier.
그럴 가능성이 있다 더 일찍 개최됩니다.
So, it's better to discuss it as early as possible.
그러니 의논해 보는 게 좋을 것 같아요 가능한 한 일찍.
Yuri, what's with that festival?
유리야, 그 축제는 뭐야?
David. Will you please explain to Jay-jay what the festival is?
데이비드. 설명해 주시겠어요? Jay-jay에게 축제는 무엇인가요?
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
So, the school festival. It's a week-long celebration.
그래서 학교 축제. 일주일간 열리는 축제입니다.
There's a sports fest, food stalls, booths, and a program.
스포츠 축제가 있어요. 음식 가판대, 부스 및 프로그램.
Whatever happens depends on the rules of the school.
무슨 일이 일어나든 상황에 따라 달라집니다 학교 규칙에 따라.
There are rules?
규칙이 있나요?
The number of booths depends on the number of section representatives.
부스 수에 따라 다름 섹션 대표 수에 관한 것입니다.
As for the program, as usual, it's going to be a pageant.
프로그램에 관해서는 평소와 같이 그것은 미인 대회가 될 것입니다.
Another pageant?
또 다른 미인대회?
Freya's gonna win again.
프레야가 또 이길 거예요.
When it comes to tasks, A is in charge of the program.
과제에 관해서는, A씨는 프로그램을 담당하고 있다.
B for sports.
스포츠의 경우 B.
C for booths.
C는 부스입니다.
And D is tasked with security.
그리고 D는 보안을 담당합니다.
And your section is night duty.
그리고 당신 구역은 야간 근무야.
What do you mean by "night duty?"
"야간 근무"란 무슨 뜻인가요?
The festival runs for a whole week.
축제는 일주일 내내 진행됩니다.
Security is also needed at night.
밤에도 보안이 필요합니다.
To watch the equipment.
장비를 보려면.
And to clean up all the garbage.
그리고 모든 쓰레기를 청소하십시오.
- That's right! - Yuck! It's disgusting!
- 좋아요! - 윽! 역겹다!
[Section E boys complaining]
[섹션 E 소년들의 불평]
You're all good at complaining, but you make me clean this place on my own!
다들 불평을 잘하시네요 그런데 당신은 나 혼자서 이곳을 청소하게 만드네요!
[Section E continues compaining]
[섹션 E는 계속해서 설명합니다]
Class, class!
수업, 수업!
They're gonna make us clean the trash! Disgusting!
그들은 우리를 만들거야 쓰레기를 청소하세요! 역겨운!
Class! Class, class.
수업! 수업, 수업.
You know the rules.
당신은 규칙을 알고 있습니다.
You won't be allowed at the festival if you don't do it.
넌 입장이 허락되지 않을 거야 안 하면 축제.
That's the old rule.
그것은 오래된 규칙입니다.
I'm the class president now, so it's going to change.
지금은 내가 반장이에요. 그래서 바뀔 것입니다.
Then what are you suggesting?
그럼 당신은 무엇을 제안하고 있습니까?
We don't do any task.
우리는 어떤 일도 하지 않습니다.
But then, you won't be allowed to the festival.
그런데 그러면 넌 안 될 거야 축제에 허용됩니다.
That's too much.
너무 많아요.
Mica and I are going on a date.
미카와 나는 데이트를 할 거예요.
I won't be able to watch Rakki's match.
라키의 경기를 볼 수 없을 것 같아요.
There's gonna be so much girls there.
거기엔 여자들이 정말 많을 거예요.
And food! Food!
그리고 음식! 음식!
Here, eat this.
자, 이것을 먹어보세요.
I wanna go too! I haven't been to the festival!
나도 가고 싶어! 나는 축제에 가본 적이 없다!
No!
아니요!
My decision is final.
내 결정은 최종적입니다.
No Festival. No tasks.
축제가 없습니다. 작업이 없습니다.
You're only thinking about yourself!
당신은 당신 자신에 대해서만 생각하고 있습니다!
I'm just trying to save this section from embarrassment.
난 그냥 이걸 저장하려고 하는 중이야 당황스러운 부분.
How about what we want?!
우리가 원하는 것은 어떻습니까?!
What's it gonna be, boys?
어떻게 될 거야, 얘들아?
Wanna be humiliated?
굴욕을 당하고 싶나요?
No...
아니...
We don't want to clean garbage.
우리는 쓰레기를 청소하고 싶지 않습니다.
- No, right? - [Section E boys complaining]
- 아니, 그렇죠? - [섹션 E 소년들이 불평함]
But! But! But!
하지만! 하지만! 하지만!
You want to go to the festival too, right?
너도 축제에 가고 싶구나, 그렇지?
Of course!
물론!
- See? See? - [Section E boys agreeing]
- 보다? 보다? - [섹션 E 소년 동의함]
There! You, wanna go? Two, three, four, five.
거기! 당신, 갈래요? 둘, 셋, 넷, 다섯.
Class...
수업...
Then choose!
그럼 선택하세요!
Deal with the garbage...
쓰레기를 처리하세요...
or hang out somewhere nice?
아니면 좋은 곳에서 놀까?
Hang out!
놀다!
Wait, wait, wait.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐.
Or how about this... enjoy the festival or just rot at home?
아니면 이건 어때요... 축제를 즐길 것인가, 아니면 그냥 집에서 썩을 것인가?
- The Festival is more fun! - Let's just hangout!
- 축제가 더 재미있어요! - 그냥 놀자!
[Section E arguing]
[섹션 E 논쟁]
Class! Class!
수업! 수업!
- The festival's better, right? - Enough, enough.
- 축제가 더 좋지 않나요? - 충분해요, 충분해요.
Enough.
충분한.
The board hasn't finalized the festival date yet.
이사회가 아직 확정되지 않았습니다. 축제 날짜는 아직.
You still have time to decide what you want to do.
아직 결정할 시간이 있어요 당신이하고 싶은 것.
Now, let's just go back to our lesson.
이제 우리 수업으로 돌아가 보겠습니다.
We'll be discussing the literary structure particular
우리는 다음에 대해 논의할 것입니다. 문학적 구조 특정
[Jay-jay exhales]
[제이제이가 숨을 내쉰다]
Here's my favorite subject.
여기 제가 가장 좋아하는 주제가 있습니다.
Lunch break.
점심 시간.
- Oh! - There you go!
- 오! - 됐어요!
Oh, Jay!
아, 제이!
It's just gonna be us and David later, right?
그냥 우리뿐일 거야 그리고 나중에 데이빗도 있지, 그렇지?
Maybe. Let's just be together.
아마도. 그냥 함께 있자.
Be together?
함께 있어?
Stop fooling around.
장난은 그만둬.
- You're gonna get it from me. - Tss.
- 당신이 나한테서 그걸 얻을 거예요. - 쉿.
I'm just kidding.
농담이에요.
Why don't we eat?
우리는 왜 먹지 않습니까?
Let's go upstairs.
위층으로 가자.
Go ahead. I'll go after you, guys.
계속하세요. 내가 쫓아갈게, 얘들아.
Bring this with you.
이것을 가지고 오십시오.
Yuri! I'll be there in a bit. I'll just do something.
유리! 조금 있으면 도착할 거예요. 그냥 뭔가를 할게요.
Ah…
아...
- We can wait for you. - Are you sure, Jay?
- 우리는 당신을 기다릴 수 있습니다. - 확실해요, 제이?
Yeah, yeah.
응, 응.
Alright.
괜찮은.
- Let's go, baby. - I'm excited to eat.
- 가자, 자기야. - 먹을 생각에 신난다.
Here.
여기.
Eat here.
여기서 먹어라.
No way.
안 돼요.
Why do you have to eat there?
왜 거기서 밥을 먹어야 해?
Because we want to.
우리가 원하기 때문에.
Are you really going to dictate where we eat?
정말 가시나요? 우리가 어디서 먹을지 지시할 수 있나요?
Josh!
조롱!
Call Calix and the others.
Calix와 다른 사람들에게 전화하십시오.
- Calix! - Huh?
- 칼릭스! - 뭐?
- Keifer wants you back here. - What now?
- 키퍼가 당신이 여기로 돌아오길 원해요. - 지금은요?
Oh, what is it?
아, 그게 뭐죠?
I don't really know. He's mad.
나는 정말로 모른다. 그는 화가 났어요.
What the heck.
대체 뭐야?
Starting today...
오늘부터...
No one will eat upstairs.
위층에는 아무도 식사를 하지 않을 거예요.
Everyone will stay here.
다들 여기 남을 거예요.
Mica… Go on. Sit over there.
운모… 계속하세요. 저기 앉으세요.
Sit there, Calix.
거기 앉아요, 칼릭스.
Food!
음식!
And!
그리고!
No one will steal another's food.
누구도 다른 사람의 음식을 훔치지 않습니다.
Bring your own food.
음식을 직접 가져오세요.
Cool.
시원한.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Yuri, let's sit together.
유리야, 같이 앉자.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Here's mine.
여기 내 것이 있습니다.
Yuri.
유리.
You're in my seat.
당신은 내 자리에 있습니다.
Move.
이동하다.
Jay, what's your food?
제이, 음식은 뭐예요?
This…
이…
I brought your favorite.
당신이 가장 좋아하는 것을 가져 왔습니다.
Wanna trade?
거래하고 싶나요?
Sure.
확신하는.
Cool.
시원한.
- Thank you, Yuri. - Thanks, too.
- 고마워요, 유리. - 나도 고마워요.
Yes, let's eat!
응, 먹자!
Thank you.
감사합니다.
- Can I have some? - Hey, this is so tasty!
- 좀 먹어도 될까요? - 야 이거 너무 맛있어!
Let me try some.
좀 시도해 보겠습니다.
Uhh, Jay… aren't we gonna give them some?
어, 제이… 그렇지 않나요? 그들에게 좀 줄까?
Yeah…
응...
Don't you feel sorry for us?
우리한테 미안하지 않니?
We look like beggars here.
여기 우리는 거지처럼 보입니다.
Especially this one. He also smells like one.
특히 이건요. 그에게서도 냄새가 난다.
Ouch.
아야.
Boys,
얘들아,
I apologize. The Old Man caught me.
사과드립니다. 노인이 나를 잡았습니다.
I can't bring food for you anymore.
더 이상 음식을 가져올 수 없습니다.
I have an idea!
나한테 아이디어가 있어!
Why don't we cook for them?
우리가 그들을 위해 요리하는 게 어때요?
We have some kitchenware here, right?
우리에겐 좀 있어요 여기 주방용품 맞죠?
Don't touch those.
그것들을 만지지 마세요.
Once is enough.
한 번이면 충분합니다.
Here's your food. Let's eat this.
여기 음식이 있습니다. 이것을 먹자.
Give me some!
나 좀 줘!
We're not gonna touch those anymore.
우리는 더 이상 그것들을 건드리지 않을 것입니다.
Those aren't ours.
그것들은 우리 것이 아닙니다.
What if we break them?
우리가 그걸 부수면 어쩌지?
Who owns them?
누가 그것을 소유합니까?
Superman.
초인.
It's Eman.
에만이에요.
He's our classmate, but he's been skipping school.
그 사람은 우리 반 친구예요. 하지만 그 사람은 학교를 빼먹었어요.
Where is he? Why is he skipping classes?
그는 어디에 있나요? 왜 그 사람은 수업을 빼먹었어?
He's at their restaurant.
그 사람 식당에 있어요.
I heard…
들었어...
I heard that their business is failing, so he has to work.
사업이 망하고 있다는 소식을 들었는데, 그래서 그는 일해야 해요.
Why him? Where are his parents?
왜 그 사람입니까? 그의 부모는 어디에 있나요?
God,
맙소사,
his mother is a good-for-nothing spendthrift.
그의 어머니는 쓸데없는 낭비꾼.
His father got into an accident.
그의 아버지가 사고를 당했습니다.
Burned his arm while cooking.
요리를 하다가 팔에 화상을 입었습니다.
That's unfortunate.
불행한 일이군요.
Shall we visit him?
그를 만나러 갈까요?
Tss!
쯧쯧!
You're meddling again.
당신은 또 간섭하고 있습니다.
Sure. I'll come with you later.
확신하는. 나중에 같이 갈게요.
Me too.
저도요.
Okay, I'll go too.
알았어, 나도 갈게.
Let's go as well, baby.
우리도 가자, 자기야.
Mmhm.
음.
Are we here?
우리 여기 있나요?
Does Eman's family really own this?
Eman의 가족이 정말로 이것을 소유하고 있습니까?
So cool.
정말 멋지다.
Have you been here? Looks like their food's delicious.
여기에 가본 적이 있나요? 그 음식이 맛있는 것 같군요.
I wonder what their specialty is.
그들의 전공이 무엇인지 궁금합니다.
See? You can't say no to us.
보다? 당신은 우리에게 거절할 수 없습니다.
- Five more minutes, sir. - Are you serious?
- 5분만 더 기다리세요. - 진심이에요?
I'm really sorry. Wait just a moment.
정말 죄송해요. 잠시만 기다리십시오.
Welcome.
환영.
Good morning. Are you open?
좋은 아침이에요. 열려 있나요?
Yes. Table for how many?
예. 테이블은 몇 명인가요?
He's asking us.
그는 우리에게 묻고 있습니다.
We're not here to eat. Remember?
우리는 식사하러 온 것이 아닙니다. 기억하다?
Is Eman here?
에만 여기 있어요?
He's in the kitchen. Do you need anything from him?
그는 부엌에 있어요. 그 사람한테 필요한 게 있나요?
Tell him Section E is here.
E섹션이 여기 있다고 전해 주세요.
Tell him to come out and don't keep us waiting.
그 사람한테 나오라고 해 그리고 우리를 기다리게 하지 마세요.
Please.
제발.
I'll handle this.
이건 제가 처리하겠습니다.
Alright.
괜찮은.
What do you need?
뭐가 필요하세요?
We want to know how you're doing.
우리는 당신이 어떻게 지내는지 알고 싶습니다.
Then you can feed us after.
그러면 나중에 우리에게 먹이를 줄 수 있습니다.
Is that really why you're here?
그게 정말 당신이 여기 온 이유인가요?
No. I want to ask permission to use your things back at school.
아니요. 허락을 구하고 싶습니다. 학교에 있는 물건을 다시 사용하기 위해.
Maybe we can borrow them.
어쩌면 빌릴 수도 있을 것 같아요.
Use them.
그것들을 사용하세요.
Do what you want.
원하는 대로 하세요.
I'm gonna quit school so… you can have those.
나 학교 그만둘 거야 그래서… 당신은 그것을 가질 수 있습니다.
Is that true?
그게 사실인가요?
You're really gonna quit?
정말 그만둘 건가요?
You see my situation here.
여기 내 상황이 보입니다.
I'm needed at the restaurant.
나는 식당에 필요해요.
Only three of us are left here.
여기에는 우리 중 세 명만 남았습니다.
Are you managing the restaurant?
식당을 관리하고 계시나요?
Your dad was the chef here, right?
너희 아버지가 여기 셰프셨지?
Who's cooking?
누가 요리하고 있나요?
Now?
지금?
It's me.
나야.
What's taking so long?!
왜 이렇게 오래 걸리나요?!
I apologize, sir.
사과드립니다.
I have to go back to the kitchen. We have customers.
나는 다시 돌아가야 해 부엌. 우리에게는 고객이 있습니다.
Hey, Eman!
안녕, 에만!
We're not done talking to you.
아직 얘기가 끝나지 않았습니다.
Please.
제발.
I have work to do.
나는 할 일이 있다.
So, what's your plan?
그래서, 당신의 계획은 무엇입니까?
Right now?
지금 바로?
Go back to work.
다시 일하러 가세요.
Ma'am, sir. Please take a seat and wait. We apologize.
부인, 선생님. 자리에 앉아 기다려주세요. 사과드립니다.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Here's our menu.
여기 메뉴가 있습니다.
- Thank you.
- 감사합니다.
We're gonna help here.
우리가 도와드리겠습니다.
What?
무엇?
We're gonna help until your restaurant recovers.
우리는 그 때까지 도와줄 거예요 당신의 레스토랑이 회복되었습니다.
Until you're able to hire more crew.
더 많은 승무원을 고용할 수 있을 때까지.
And who's "we"?
그리고 "우리"는 누구입니까?
Calix and I will help.
Calix와 제가 도와드리겠습니다.
And me. I'll help out too.
그리고 나. 나도 도와줄게.
Alright, me too.
알았어, 나도 마찬가지야.
We can do shifting amongst ourselves.
우리는 우리 자신 사이에서 변화를 할 수 있습니다.
Yeah, and then just pay us with food.
응, 그럼 그냥 음식값으로 갚아라.
It's obvious I can't stop you.
내가 당신을 막을 수 없다는 것은 분명합니다.
Brother… please guide them.
형님... 지도해 주세요.
Make sure they're not gonna cause any problems.
그렇지 않은지 확인하세요. 문제가 생길 겁니다.
Bro, I'll handle that.
형, 그건 제가 처리할게요.
Tss.
쯧쯧.
Miss Meddler strikes again.
Miss Meddler가 다시 공격합니다.
Ma'am, sir. Here's your order.
부인, 선생님. 주문 내용은 다음과 같습니다.
Oh, thank you.
아, 고마워요.
Are you ready to order?
주문할 준비가 되셨나요?
Baby, there's a customer.
자기야, 손님이 왔어.
We have all meat pizza…
고기 피자는 다 있어요...
standard pizza...
표준 피자...
Do you have extra aprons?
여분의 앞치마가 있나요?
Ma'am, What's your order?
부인, 주문이 어떻게 되세요?
Do you want to try this?
이것을 시도 하시겠습니까?
Calix.
칼리스.
You're gonna try everything? Here's our bestseller.
모든 것을 시도해 볼 건가요? 여기 베스트셀러가 있습니다.
That soup.
그 수프.
For drinks, we have juices, hot drinks, soft drinks…
음료로는 주스도 있고, 뜨거운 음료, 청량음료…
Everything.
모든 것.
Everything?
모든 것?
I'll tell the rest of the class myself.
나머지 수업시간에는 제가 직접 말씀드리겠습니다.
- Oh, alright. - Have you dined here before, Miss?
- 아, 알았어. - 전에 여기서 식사하신 적 있나요, 아가씨?
You know our menu!
우리 메뉴 아시죠?
- Here's your order, Sir. - Thank you.
- 명령은 여기 있습니다, 선생님. - 감사합니다.
Enjoy your meal.
식사를 즐기십시오.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Smile.
웃다.
What?
무엇?
Like this.
이와 같이.
There!
거기!
He's so handsome.
그는 너무 잘생겼어요.
Go on.
계속하세요.
Smile, okay?
웃어, 알았지?
He's coming, he's coming.
그가 온다, 그가 온다.
Your orders are coming up.
귀하의 주문이 곧 다가오고 있습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
[customers screaming]
[비명을 지르는 고객]
Heres' your change.
여기 잔돈이 있습니다.
Do you have any additional orders?
추가 주문이 있으신가요?
Thank you! Did you like the food?
감사합니다! 음식이 마음에 드셨나요?
It was delicious. We're gonna come back.
맛있었습니다. 우리는 돌아올 것이다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Your service was exemplary.
귀하의 서비스는 모범적이었습니다.
Thank you very much.
매우 감사합니다.
5 star!
별 5개!
Wow.
우와.
Thank you!
감사합니다!
Oh, please come see us again.
아, 꼭 다시 만나러 오세요.
Take care. Please do come back.
잘 지내세요. 꼭 다시 와주세요.
Oh.
오.
I thought you're gonna help?
당신이 도와줄 거라고 생각했어요?
Did I say that?
내가 그렇게 말했나요?
Oh gosh,
이런,
you're miles behind Yuri.
당신은 유리보다 몇 마일 뒤쳐져 있어요.
Look.
바라보다.
Baby!
아기!
Thank you.
감사합니다.
My baby is so cute.
우리 아기는 너무 귀여워요.
- You're from HVIS, right? Grade 12? - Yeah.
- HVIS 출신이지? 12학년? - 응.
I saw you at school. Red hair. It's really you!
학교에서 봤어요. 빨간 머리. 정말 당신이에요!
Look at Yuri.
유리를 보세요.
Do what he's doing.
그가 하는 일을 하세요.
Just stay here, okay?
그냥 여기 있어, 알았지?
Okay, we're really not going anywhere.
좋아요, 우리는 정말 아무데도 가지 않을 거예요.
Hey,
안녕,
our shift's not over yet.
우리 근무시간은 아직 끝나지 않았어.
The others are still coming...
다른 사람들은 아직 오고 있어요...
Ah.
아.
[customers screaming]
[비명을 지르는 고객]
Look over there.
저기 좀 보세요.
What happened to him?
그에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Are you ready to order?
주문할 준비가 되셨나요?
The winds have changed direction, huh?
바람은 방향을 바꿨어, 응?
[customers screaming]
[비명을 지르는 고객]
But it's effective, isn't it?
하지만 효과적이지 않나요?
So… can you just repeat your order?
그럼... 다시 주문해 주시겠어요?
Hey! What are you doing?
여기요! 뭐하세요?
It's scorching hot in here.
여기는 정말 덥습니다.
What's your order?
당신의 주문은 무엇입니까?
That's okay.
괜찮습니다.
Just seeing you is enough for us.
우리는 당신을 보는 것만으로도 충분합니다.
Here's your order.
주문 내용은 다음과 같습니다.
[screaming continues]
[비명 계속]
Of course, I'm gonna come back for you.
물론이죠. 저는 당신을 위해 다시 돌아올 것입니다.
Are you sure that's all you're gonna order?
정말로 주문할 게 그것뿐이겠어요?
Sis?
언니?
- You? Can we order you? - Picture? How about a picture? A selfie.
- 너? 주문할 수 있나요? - 그림? 사진은 어때요? 셀카.
- Selfie? - Sure.
- 셀카요? - 확신하는.
Go on, eat.
어서 먹어라.
To check your order…
주문을 확인하려면...
one order of everything in the menu.
메뉴에 있는 모든 것을 한 번에 주문하세요.
Can I touch your biceps?
팔뚝 만져봐도 될까요?
You wanna feel it?
느껴보고 싶나요?
Can we touch it again?
다시 만져볼까요?
Go on.
계속하세요.
What's up, boys?
무슨 일이야, 얘들 아?
Yo!
에야디야!
[Section E boys greeting each other]
[서로 인사하는 섹션 E 소년들]
Because of my meddling,
내 간섭 때문에
we were able to help Eman and his family.
우리는 Eman과 그의 가족을 도울 수 있었습니다.
I hope they all stay like this.
모두 이대로 있었으면 좋겠습니다.
Oh! Hey!
오! 여기요!
Ouch!
아야!
Ci! Ci! Wipe the floor, please.
시! 시! 바닥을 닦아주세요.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Go sit over here.
여기 가서 앉으세요.
Just sit down.
그냥 앉으세요.
Put it down. Sit over here.
내려 놔. 여기 앉으세요.
Go on, sit.
어서 앉으세요.
Eman, do you have a first aid kit?
이만, 구급상자 있나요?
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Let me see it.
좀 보도록 할게요.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
미안해요, 미안해요, 미안해요.
You know this is your fault, right?
이게 네 잘못인 거 알지?
Okay, already.
알았어, 벌써.
I'm treating your wound now, right?
지금은 상처를 치료하고 있는 중이잖아요?
Why do you have to meddle in things?
왜 일에 간섭해야 합니까?
Why don't you just let things be?
그냥 내버려 두는 게 어때요?
Give it to me.
나에게 주세요.
What's the reason?
이유는 무엇입니까?
Huh?
뭐?
Why can't stay away from other people's problems?
왜 멀리 갈 수 없는가? 다른 사람의 문제?
Sorry, sorry.
미안해요, 미안해요.
I just can't help it.
나는 그것을 도울 수 없습니다.
I can't just do nothing...
아무것도 할 수 없어...
when I know things can change.
상황이 바뀔 수 있다는 걸 알았을 때.
But nobody even tries.
하지만 아무도 시도조차 하지 않습니다.
Nobody believes.
아무도 믿지 않습니다.
If things can get better, why not do something about it?
상황이 나아질 수 있다면 왜 그것에 대해 뭔가를하지 않습니까?
You know you can't change everyone.
모든 사람을 바꿀 수는 없다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
At least I tried.
적어도 나는 노력했다.
Hmm.
흠.
We're even now.
우리는 지금도 그렇습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
OMG.
어머나.
So it's true. You're also a waitress now.
그래서 그것은 사실입니다. 당신도 지금은 웨이트리스야.
Keifer Watson. Is your family getting poor now?
키퍼 왓슨. 당신의 가족입니까? 지금은 가난해지고 있어?
How did Aries know we're here?
양자리는 우리가 여기 있다는 걸 어떻게 알았나요?
Will they cause a scene here?
여기서 소동이 일어날까요?
Why would Kiko suddenly court you?!
키코가 갑자기 왜 당신을 구애하겠어요?!
And you're letting him?!
그런데 당신이 그 사람을 허락하는 겁니까?!
The thing is…
문제는…
You like him.
당신은 그를 좋아합니다.
No. I'm not letting him court me.
아니요. 허락하지 않습니다 그 사람이 나한테 구애해.
You were smitten by his American accent and sweet smiles.
당신은 그에게 반했습니다 미국식 억양과 달콤한 미소.
That's not true.
그것은 사실이 아닙니다.
You don't like English-speaking guys?
영어하는 남자를 좋아하지 않나요?
No.
아니요.
How about Keifer?
케이퍼는 어때요?
[Ci-N teasing Jay-jay]
[제이제이를 놀리는 씨엔]
Will you stop that?!
그만할래?!
Do you really like Jay-jay?
제이제이를 정말 좋아하시나요?
Jay-jay is not allowed to have a boyfriend.
Jay-jay는 허용되지 않습니다 남자친구를 가지려고.
What is wrong with you?
당신에게 무슨 문제가 있습니까?
You know me.
당신은 나를 알고 있습니다.
Exactly.
정확히.
- Hey! - [ Jay-jay gets startled]
- 여기요! - [ 제이제이가 깜짝 놀란다]
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
Get in.
타세요.
Why do you need to fetch me?
왜 나를 데려와야 해요?
You want some?
좀 드시겠어요?
I know you do.
나는 당신이 알고 있습니다.
There's something different about you.
뭔가가 있어요 당신은 다릅니다.
Are you wearing contacts?
연락처를 착용하고 있나요?
Oh no… what happened to you?
아, 아니... 무슨 일이 일어난 거야?
Fuck them!
젠장!
We should retaliate. Who's with me?
우리는 보복해야 합니다. 나와 함께있는 사람은 누구입니까?
You can't come, Jay.
넌 올 수 없어, 제이.
And why not?
그리고 왜 안돼?
Because you're gonna fight again, don't you?
왜냐면 당신은 할 거니까 또 싸워, 응?
You're putting yourselves in danger because of me.
당신은 자신을두고 있습니다 나 때문에 위험해.